<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Arbiter Program]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Arbiter Program</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:52:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:52:05 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Index]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello]]></description><link>index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Index.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 05:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Plot Map]]></title><description><![CDATA[Arbiter Program - IntroThe player follows the instructions and goes to Sector-2, following signs.The player attacks the WISE agents.The player is defeated by the WISE agents.The agents declare that since they've found the player, their next objective is to recover some important documents from Sector-3. Along the way, they explain the threat of aberrations to the player, describing them as volatile entities born from the darkest corners of the human mind. Upon reaching Sector 3, they are attacked by aberrations. The agents instruct the player to stay put as they handle the situation.The player ignores the announcement and goes to Sector-3, a hallway marked by flickering lights.The WISE agents subdue the player, pressing an inhaler onto their face. Within seconds, the hazy appearance clears and the agents' voices can be heard again. The agents warn the player that using the Radiance can affect their mind, dissuading them from using their abilities.Blue - DecisionYellow - ConditionRed - Story NodeGame OverThe player was alone.The player had been separated from the WISE agents. As they cleared the darkness with their new ability, they made out the figures of the agents approaching them. However, they appeared hazy, and seemed to be shooting at the player. Their voices were distorted, a combination of garbled shouts and whispering. The words "neutralize" can be heard from an agent as another rapidly approaches the player.The player was accompanying WISE.The player defeats the WISE agents.The player encounters hostile aberrations, who blind them with every attack. The player eventually becomes fully blinded, but a flash of light replaces the darkness. As their vision returns, a cloaked figure stands before them. After defeating the aberrations with ease, their savior turns to them, eyes shrouded by wings sprouting from their head. They speak vague words of encouragement, stating the world may be strange but it still belongs to the player. They recover a luminous substance from the slain aberrations and hand it to the player, hesitating for a second as their hands touch. Showing the slightest change in emotion, they warn the player not to let others take it from them. They turn away and vanish into the darkness, contrasting their earlier use of light. The player learns a basic form of Radiance manipulation, allowing them to dispel visual impairments such as the darkness.The player doesn't act.The player attacks the WISE agents.The rest of the agents flee, leaving the player alone. During the rest of the playthrough, WISE-aligned characters are hostile to the player.The player awakens in the laboratory. Markings on the walls indicate they are in Sector-1. An automated message repeats on the PA system, warning listeners of aberrations and instructing all personnel to report to the evacuation zone of Sector-2.The player encounters soldiers who identify themselves as WISE agents, halting the player at gunpoint. They discuss amongst themselves and over their radios, before easing their guard. After apologizing for their scrutiny, they explain to the player that they have lost their memories. They ask the player for their compliance, claiming that they are an important individual and that their mission is to extract them to safety. In an attempt to build trust, they give the player a pistol and some body armour.The player agrees to cooperate.An agent is killed.A WISE agent reaches the player before they are able to defeat any of them.Purple - Game Event]]></description><link>plot-map.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Plot Map.canvas</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:08:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Factions]]></title><description><![CDATA[Keter
Engram Solutions
In the mid-21st century, the Republic of faced a crisis in which the overall mental state of the population began to deteriorate.
A government sanctioned and funded neurotechnology company that specializes in the research and application of the Radiance. Hokmah
World Institute of Scientific Exploration
An international organization formed by a coalition of nations dating back to the late 20th century. Their purpose is to investigate new inventions and scientific discoveries in order to establish countermeasures in the case of subsequent threats. WISE is the leading authority on science and medicine and has major influence in the lawmaking of states regarding new advancements, sometimes directly imposing regulations or restrictions. As the influence of corporations grew, WISE became susceptible to lobbying from companies whose sought to prevent their products and services from becoming obsolete due to new technologies. Following the discovery of the Radiance in the late 21st century, WISE asserted jurisdiction over all research and development efforts towards the Radiance and related technologies.Binah - Understanding / Concealment<a data-href="The Reclamation Doctrine" href="factions/the-reclamation-doctrine.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Reclamation Doctrine</a> / Church of the Holy DoctrineA megachurch size cult that was the leading corporation in monetizing religion and faith. During the worldwide crisis of the Anthropocene they were among the greatest humanitarian efforts, providing shelter and aid. This gained them favour with the people, who turned away from their collapsing governments and infrastructure. Their massive following and reach makes them as powerful as a developed nation. Members are taught to have a supremacist mindset, treating non-believers as blasphemers. A caste system was formed in which pre-catastrophe followers were considered upper-class, with company executives being the highest. New followers were bound to servitude, owing their lives to their saviors. Following the discovery of the Radiance, they are harvesting radiance in the form of faith from their followers to produce alternative medicine and luxury goods. There are many churches all around the world but the headquarters is stationed in a church-owned independent state.Significant Roles Patriarch Cardinals Archbishops
Radiance in the form of faith is transferred unrestricted through space directly to any object or target of worship. Those empowered can use abilities desired by those who supply the faith, such as healing, immortality, and smiting. While the patriarch and cardinals receive enough empowerment to live forever, only the archbishops are given enough to smite and heal on a large scale as Radiaccumulation makes them unstable. To keep them under control, subservience to the church is instilled at a young age. They can also emit radiance in a deceitful way that influences the perception and thoughts of others, such as making them appear younger in reflections or numbing chronic pain. Emissions can be captured in physical form as used to create crystal charms and incense, which the church sells to wealthy individuals and outsiders.It was found that faith can be harvested slowly through prayer, but technology developed allowed the implantation of neurotechnology that strengthened the faith and worship output of followers. These implants were applied during baptisms. but the death of devout followers can release large amounts of radiance at once. News of mysterious deaths began spreading but subsequently covered up as the actions of a great savior taking devout followers up into an afterlife paradise. This myth was taken advantage of by the church as those suffering were encouraged to become more devoted for the chance of an advance departure to the afterlife. As conflicts rose between factions, outsiders were interested in the methods of the church. In order to empower their enforcers and leaders, the church planned a mass harvest disguised as a Rapture in order to increase the faith of their followers quickly.In addition to faith, guilt can also be harvested as a form of Radiance. Confession booths in churches were converted to serve this new purpose. Priests were given a small fraction of the powers of Archbishops, allowing them to extract guilt from followers. In addition to the high presence of guilt resonant radiation in the booths, they were able to interfere with people's minds making them more susceptible to confessing their secrets. In addition, the extraction of guilt provides a sense of relief resembling weight being taken off one's conscience, a sensation followers would come back to experience again. Confession became part of culture allowing the Church to conduct mass surveillance on their citizens. Other states also formed or strengthened their partnerships with the Church to aid public security efforts through confessionals. The technology would soon spread to detective and intelligence agencies worldwide to aid with interrogations. An issue arose however, where guilt would be so overwhelming that suspects would falsely admit to crimes, starting an era of injustice.Chesed - Mercy, Benevolence / Suffocating Love
Anodyne Incorporated
An international pharmaceutical company with many subsidiaries covering healthcare, insurance, security, and research. As the catastrophes of the Anthropocene began, Anodyne worked with governments to supply humanitarian aid. Geburah - Justice, Severity, Might / Blind Violence
Initially a resistance movement against the growing presence of the Tiphareth - Beauty / Harmony / BalanceNetzach - Victory / Joy / Endurance]]></description><link>factions.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:52:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>